azubu.com 2015-04-25

# Privacy policy | Azubu

Please note that this Privacy Policy may be revised periodically by making such revisions available on the Site or otherwise providing notice to you. Thus, please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your use of the Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of the Services after any revisions to this Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to such revisions.

By using the Site or any of the Services, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

Log Data  
As you use the Services, whether as a registered or non-registered user, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site (“Log Data”). Log Data may include device-specific information such as your computer’s IP address, operating system version, browser type, unique device identifiers, mobile network information including phone number, the content and pages that you access on the Services, the dates and times that you visit the Services, device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings or browser language, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or AZUBU TV account or the Internet protocol address from which you are visiting. Log Data may also include the URL or other identifiers of the server of any link followed to reach the Site, and usage data gathered through ‘cookies’ as explained in the following paragraph. All Log Data that does not identify you will be considered Non-Identifying Information under this Privacy Policy.

Cookies  
Like many websites, we use one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to collect usage information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your encrypted registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site as well as display preference settings (such as preferred language). Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services. We collect data regarding use of the cookies to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor aggregate usage by AZUBU TV Users and web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Third-party advertisers on the Services may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can set your browser, by editing its options, to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our Services, or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services.

Information Use  
We may use the Non-Identifying Information we collect for any purpose, including the allowance of third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, please visit the following websites:

Consumer Choices Page: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>  
Network Advertising Initiative (USA and Canada): [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)  
A Guide to Behavioural Advertising (Europe): <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>

We may use the Personal Information we collect as follows.

Site Administration and Operation  
Personal Information may be stored and used to verify your identify, contact you, provide you with notifications, administer your account, provide our Services, improve our Services, create new Services, enable your use of the Site and Services, analyze AZUBU TV Users and use of the Services and related preferences, and otherwise operate the Site and Services. Personal Information may be transferred and stored anywhere in the United States of America or internationally.

Marketing and Promotions  
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with AZUBU TV newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you, including information regarding third-party products and services. AZUBU TV members who agree to the AZUBU TV Terms of Service are given the opportunity to opt-in to receiving such communications from us in the future. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing or promotional communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “user preferences” information. (See “Changing or Deleting Your Information” below.)

Information Disclosure  
We may disclose the Non-Identifying Information we collect to any party for any purpose. We may disclose the Personal Information we collect as follows.

Public Profile Information  
When you register through the Site and submit your Personal Information to create a profile webpage, AZUBU TV Users will see your screen or user name, the month and year you first registered with AZUBU TV, and any other comments or submissions that you post on the Site or submit via the Services. You can choose what other Personal Information you provide as part of your profile (“Other Member Information”) and in some cases you can choose whether to share that information publicly on the Site by making selections via user preferences section of your profile webpage. Providing Other Member Information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with AZUBU TV Users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information, and that you not use your real name as your screen or user name to the extent that allows others to identify you.

Affiliates  
AZUBU TV may also share your Personal Information with other networks, websites and entities affiliated, owned, controlled and/or connected with AZUBU TV.

Demographics and Marketing  
We may share aggregated information that includes your Personal Information, Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising about AZUBU TV or other products and services.

Promotional Partners  
We may from time to time offer special access to pay-per-view or other special promotional events, and we may share your Personal Information with those entities and advertisers that are participating in such events. Unless otherwise stated in connection with such promotion, we will only share your name and email address with such parties, so that you may receive newsletters or promotional materials from such entities.

Service Providers  
We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Site-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used (each, a “Service Provider”). The types of Service Providers we use include those that provide the following types of services: credit card processing, accounting, customer relationship management, website maintenance, notification services, database management and web analytics. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Third-Party Social Networking Services  
As an AZUBU TV member, you can link your account information with certain social networking services (“SNS”) and broadcast your activities and other data to your friends. In these instances, depending on the user preferences you set in your AZUBU TV account, with your permission and on your behalf we will share the information contained in your AZUBU TV account (e.g., AZUBU TV profile page, channel page and any other information you deem public in any content you create on the Site) with the SNS. We also receive certain information (which may include your Personal Information) in accordance with the privacy settings you have set in your SNS account, if any. Other than what we may share with the SNS in connection with your linking of accounts, the personal information SNS has about you is obtained by the SNS independently of our Services. Other services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other online services you use.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement  
AZUBU TV cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of AZUBU TV or a third party, to enforce our rights, including under our Terms of Service, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. We may also disclose any information as otherwise required by law.

Business Transfers  
We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Changing or Deleting Your Information  
All AZUBU TV members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile under account settings. Upon disabling your account, all such information previously belonging to the account will be lost. However, AZUBU TV will preserve the basic account information for 90 days subsequent to termination of service for general security purposes. We will then discard all information pertaining to your account immediately after the expiration of the 90-day grace period. If you would like to modify or delete all or parts of your record in our system, please follow the steps to disable your account on the Site. We will attempt to accommodate your request within a reasonable period of time after our receipt of your request. However, we make no exception to the previously set forth rule for retention of records.

Security  
We are very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ reasonable physical, technological and administrative security measures to protect AZUBU TV and AZUBU TV Users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. Nonetheless, please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is completely secure. Thus, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant its absolute security.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of security, confidentiality or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with the legitimate needs of law enforcement or any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

International Transfer  
Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States of America and choose to provide information to us, AZUBU TV transfers Personal Information to the United States of America and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer.

Links to Other Sites  
The Services contain links to other websites and we may allow advertisers, third-party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisement directly to you within the Services. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. We do not exercise control over third-party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through our Services and does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of such other websites you visit.

AZUBU TV reserves the right to add or remove third-party ad networks or ad servers in its sole discretion and may not at all times list such updated ad network or ad server partners in this Privacy Policy.

Our Policy Towards Children  
If you are under the age of 13, please do not use or access the Services at any time or in any manner. AZUBU TV does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without his/her consent, he or she should contact us at azubu@azubu.tv. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files and terminate the account concerned immediately.

Your California Privacy Rights  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business with whom the California resident has an established business relationship certain information with respect to the types of Personal Information the business shares with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one such request each year by e-mailing us at azubu@azubu.tv. You may also read a description of our information disclosure practices in the foregoing provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Contacting Us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@azubu.com](mailto:support@azubu.com) or at:

AZUBU North America, Inc.  
15303 Ventura Blvd Suite 220  
Sherman Oaks, CA 91403
